

Ayush Kumar Student

My Contact

□ ak0224225@gmail.com

(+91 9868642936

T-510/C-15E, New Delhi-08

soul-999-ayu.github.io/Portfolio

Hard Skill

- C, C++, JAVA, RenPy, Shell Script (Basic)
- Problem Solver
- Troubleshooting
- · Presentation Skills
- · Writing skills

Soft Skill

- **Adaptive**
- Decision making
- Communication
- Fast Learner

Education Background

- GTB INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY Computer Science - 2nd Year **Currently Pursuing**
- PUSA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY Electronics and Communication with 89.6% Completed in 2023
- P.G D.A.V SEN. SEC. School 10th with **81.2%** marks Completed in 2020

About Me

Currently a student at GTB 4th Centenary from CSE Branch. Have 2 year of coding experience in JAVA and currently learning RenPy. My future goal is to get a job in which I can help others using my skills in coding and my knowledge in Electronics.

Professional Experience

Max Engg. and Automation | Intern

June 2022 - July 2022

Key learnings:

- Learnt about PLC, SCADA, Vijeo designer basic
- Learnt the ladder language for PLC Programming

Bentext Pvt. Ltd. | Intern

May 2022 - June 2022

Key learnings:

- Learnt about **Electric meter**
- Learnt about Its circuit
- Prepared reports on the above information and reported the insights.

Achievements

2022-2023 Developed many programs like

> ChatGPT-ChatBot, Password Manager, Music Player, I Wonder (Visual Novel) using Java and RenPy

and uploaded them on GitHub.

Developed many (almost 100) custom 2021-2022

roms for Redmi Y1 and Y1 lite and was

acknowledged by Nippon and Cafebabe (Poppular developers).

Projects

Automatic Door opening system using 6th sem

Arduino as Major Project.

Wireless Charger as Minor Project. 4th sem